<document>
<fileid id='a0001_001'>
Author of the danger trail, Philip Steels, etcetera.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_002'>
Not at this particular case, Tom, apologized Whittemore.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_003'>
For the twentieth time that evening the two men shook hands.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_004'>
Lord, but I'm glad to see you again, Phil.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_005'>
Will we ever forget it.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_006'>
God bless 'em, I hope I'll go on seeing them forever.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_007'>
And you always want to see it in the superlative degree.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_008'>
Gad, your letter came just in time.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_009'>
He turned sharply, and faced Gregson across the table.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_010'>
I'm playing a single hand in what looks like a losing game.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_011'>
If I ever needed a fighter in my life I need one now.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_012'>
Gregson shoved back his chair and rose to his feet.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_013'>
He was a head shorter than his companion, of almost delicate physique.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_014'>
Now you're coming down to business, Phil, he exclaimed.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_015'>
It's the aurora borealis.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_016'>
There's Fort Churchill, a rifle-shot beyond the ridge, asleep.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_017'>
From that moment his friendship for Belize turns to hatred and jealousy.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_018'>
There was a change now.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_019'>
I followed the line of the proposed railroad, looking for chances.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_020'>
Clubs and balls and cities grew to be only memories.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_021'>
It fairly clubbed me into recognizing it.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_022'>
Hardly were our plans made public before we were met by powerful opposition.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_023'>
A combination of Canadian capital quickly organized and petitioned for the same privileges.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_024'>
It was my reports from the north which chiefly induced people to buy.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_025'>
I was about to do this when cooler judgment prevailed.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_026'>
It occurred to me that there would have to be an accounting.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_027'>
To my surprise he began to show actual enthusiasm in my favor.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_028'>
Robbery, bribery, fraud, 
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_029'>
Their forces were already moving into the north country.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_030'>
I had faith in them.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_031'>
They were three hundred yards apart.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_032'>
Since then some mysterious force has been fighting us at every step.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_033'>
He unfolded a long typewritten letter, and handed it to Gregson.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_034'>
Men of Selden's stamp don't stop at women and children.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_035'>
He stopped, and Philip nodded at the horrified question in his eyes.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_036'>
She turned in at the hotel.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_037'>
I was the only one who remained sitting.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_038'>
We'll have to watch our chances.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_039'>
The ship should be in within a week or ten days.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_040'>
I suppose you wonder why she is coming up here.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_041'>
Meanwhile I'll go out to breathe a spell.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_042'>
How could he explain his possession of the sketch.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_043'>
It seemed nearer to him since he had seen and talked with Gregson.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_044'>
Her own betrayal of herself was like tonic to Philip.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_045'>
He moved away as quietly as he had come.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_046'>
The girl faced him, her eyes shining with sudden fear.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_047'>
Close beside him gleamed the white fangs of the wolf-dog.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_048'>
He looked at the handkerchief more, closely.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_049'>
Gregson was asleep when he re-entered the cabin.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_050'>
In spite of their absurdity the words affected Philip curiously.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_051'>
The lace was of a delicate ivory color, faintly tinted with yellow.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_052'>
It was a curious coincidence.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_053'>
Suddenly his fingers closed tightly over the handkerchief.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_054'>
There was nothing on the rock.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_055'>
Philip stood undecided, his ears strained to catch the slightest sound.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_056'>
Pearce's little eyes were fixed on him shrewdly.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_057'>
I have no idea, replied Philip.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_058'>
I came for information more out of curiosity than anything else.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_059'>
His immaculate appearance was gone.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_060'>
Anyway, no one saw her like that.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_061'>
Philip snatched at the letter which Gregson held out to him.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_062'>
The men stared into each other's face.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_063'>
Yes, it was a man who asked, a stranger.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_064'>
The fourth and fifth days passed without any developments.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_065'>
They closed now until his fingers were like cords of steel.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_066'>
He saw Jeanne falter for a moment.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_067'>
Surely I will excuse you, she cried.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_068'>
In a flash Philip followed its direction.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_069'>
It was his intention to return to Eileen and her father.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_070'>
He would first hunt up Gregson and begin his work there.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_071'>
What was the object of your little sensation.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_072'>
But who was Eileen's double.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_073'>
The promoter's eyes were heavy, with little puffy bags under them.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_074'>
And now, down there, Eileen was waiting for him.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_075'>
There has been a change, she interrupted him.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_076'>
The gray eyes faltered; the flush deepened.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_077'>
It is the fire, partly, she said.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_078'>
Then, and at supper, he tried to fathom her.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_079'>
It was a large canoe.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_080'>
What if Jeanne failed him.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_081'>
What if she did not come to the rock.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_082'>
His face was streaming with blood.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_083'>
A shadow was creeping over Pierre's eyes.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_084'>
Scarcely had he uttered the name when Pierre's closing eyes shot open.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_085'>
A trickle of fresh blood ran over his face.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_086'>
Death had come with terrible suddenness.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_087'>
Philip bent lower, and stared into the face of the dead man.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_088'>
He made sure that the magazine was loaded, and resumed his paddling.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_089'>
The nightglow was treacherous to shoot by.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_090'>
The singing voice approached rapidly.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_091'>
His blood grew hot with rage at the thought.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_092'>
He went down in midstream, searching the shadows of both shores.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_093'>
For a full minute he crouched and listened.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_094'>
He had barely entered this when he saw the glow of a fire.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_095'>
A big canvas tent was the first thing to come within his vision.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_096'>
Perhaps she had already met her fate a little deeper in the forest.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_097'>
Then you can arrange yourself comfortably among these robes in the bow.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_098'>
Shall I carry you.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_099'>
A maddening joy pounded in his brain.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_100'>
You must sleep, he urged.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_101'>
You, you would not keep the truth from me.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_102'>
He will follow us soon.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_103'>
But there came no promise from the bow of the canoe.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_104'>
She was sleeping under his protection as sweetly as a child.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_105'>
Only, it is so wonderful, so almost impossible to believe.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_106'>
The emotion which she had suppressed burst forth now in a choking sob.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_107'>
If you only could know how I thank you.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_108'>
He waded into the edge of the water and began scrubbing himself.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_109'>
Do you know that you are shaking my confidence in you.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_110'>
Much, replied Jeanne, as tersely.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_111'>
Instead, he joined her; and they ate like two hungry children.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_112'>
He was wounded in the arm.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_113'>
I suppose you picked that lingo up among the Indians.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_114'>
Her words sent a strange chill through Philip.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_115'>
He had no excuse for the feelings which were aroused in him.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_116'>
Was it the rendezvous of those who were striving to work his ruin.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_117'>
She added, with genuine sympathy in her face and voice.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_118'>
Pierre obeys me when we are together.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_119'>
Jeanne was turning the bow shoreward.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_120'>
My right foot feels like that of a Chinese debutante.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_121'>
They ate dinner at the fifth, and rested for two hours.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_122'>
Two years ago I gave up civilization for this.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_123'>
She had died from cold and starvation.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_124'>
It was Jeanne singing softly over beyond the rocks.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_125'>
He was determined now to maintain a more certain hold upon himself.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_126'>
Each day she became a more vital part of him.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_127'>
It was a temptation, but he resisted it.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_128'>
This one hope was destroyed as quickly as it was born.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_129'>
Her face was against his breast.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_130'>
She was his now, forever.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_131'>
Providence had delivered him through the maelstrom.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_132'>
A cry of joy burst from Philip's lips.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_133'>
Philip began to feel that he had foolishly overestimated his strength.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_134'>
He obeyed the pressure of her hand.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_135'>
I am going to surprise father, and you will go with Pierre.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_136'>
About him, everywhere, were the evidences of luxury and of age.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_137'>
Then he stepped back with a low cry of pleasure.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_138'>
In the picture he saw each moment a greater resemblance to Jeanne.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_139'>
He told himself that as he washed himself and groomed his disheveled clothes.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_140'>
Accept a father's blessing, and with it, this.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_141'>
It seems like a strange pointing of the hand of God.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_142'>
Such things had occurred before, he told Philip.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_143'>
Ah, I had forgotten, he exclaimed.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_144'>
But there was something even more startling than this resemblance.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_145'>
I have to be careful of them, as they tear very easily.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_146'>
Of course, that is uninteresting, she continued.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_147'>
A moment before he was intoxicated by a joy that was almost madness.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_148'>
Now these things had been struck dead within him.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_149'>
For an instant he saw Pierre drawn like a silhouette against the sky.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_150'>
Goodbye, Pierre, he shouted.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_151'>
And MacDougall was beyond the trail, with three weeks to spare.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_152'>
Philip thrust himself against it and entered.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_153'>
MacDougall tapped his forehead suspiciously with a stubby forefinger.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_154'>
He was smooth-shaven, and his hair and eyes were black.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_155'>
Won't you draw up, gentlemen.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_156'>
A strange fire burned in his eyes when Thorpe turned.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_157'>
He had worshiped her, as Dante might have worshiped Beatrice.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_158'>
Does that look good.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_159'>
They look as though he had been drumming a piano all his life.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_160'>
You want to go over and see his gang throw dirt.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_161'>
Take away their foreman and they wouldn't be worth their grub.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_162'>
That's the sub-foreman, explained Thorpe.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_163'>
Philip made no effort to follow.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_164'>
He came first a year ago, and revealed himself to Jeanne.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_165'>
They are to attack your camp tomorrow night.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_166'>
Two days ago Jeanne learned where her father's men were hiding.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_167'>
I was near the cabin, and saw you.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_168'>
Low bush whipped him in the face and left no sting.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_169'>
Suddenly Jeanne stopped for an instant.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_170'>
There was none of the joy of meeting in his face.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_171'>
And when you come back in a few days, bring Eileen.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_172'>
Gregson had left the outer door slightly ajar.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_173'>
The date was nearly eighteen years old.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_174'>
They were the presage of storm.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_175'>
Down there the earth was already swelling with life.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_176'>
For the first time in his life he was yearning for a scrap.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_177'>
She had been thoroughly and efficiently mauled.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_178'>
Every bone in her aged body seemed broken or dislocated.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_179'>
Tomorrow I'm going after that bear, he said.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_180'>
If not, let's say our prayers and go to bed.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_181'>
So cheer up, and give us your paw.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_182'>
This time he did not yap for mercy.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_183'>
And the air was growing chilly.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_184'>
Don't you see, I'm chewing this thing in two.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_185'>
The questions may have come vaguely in his mind.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_186'>
Like a flash he launched himself into the feathered mass of the owl.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_187'>
Ahead of them they saw a glimmer of sunshine.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_188'>
Two gigantic owls were tearing at the carcass.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_189'>
The big-eyed, clucking moose-birds were most annoying.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_190'>
Next to them the Canada jays were most persistent.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_191'>
For a time the exciting thrill of his adventure was gone.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_192'>
He did not rush in.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_193'>
It was edged with ice.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_194'>
He drank of the water cautiously.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_195'>
But a strange thing happened.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_196'>
He began to follow the footprints of the dog.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_197'>
Such a dog the wise driver kills, or turns loose.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_198'>
Sometimes her dreams were filled with visions.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_199'>
Thus had the raw wilderness prepared him for this day.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_200'>
He leapt again, and the club caught him once more.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_201'>
He cried, and swung the club wildly.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_202'>
She turned, fearing that Jacques might see what was in her face.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_203'>
They were following the shore of a lake.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_204'>
The wolf-dog thrust his gaunt muzzle toward him.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_205'>
From now on we're pals.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_206'>
He says he bought him of Jacques Le Beau.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_207'>
How much was it.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_208'>
Youth had come back to her, freed from the yoke of oppression.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_209'>
It was not a large lake, and almost round.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_210'>
Its diameter was not more than two hundred yards.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_211'>
It drowned all sound that brute agony and death may have made.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_212'>
Fresh cases, still able to walk, they clustered about the spokesman.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_213'>
Between him and the beach was the cane-grass fence of the compound.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_214'>
Besides, he was paid one case of tobacco per head.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_215'>
They die out of spite.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_216'>
The other felt a sudden wave of irritation rush through him.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_217'>
Oppressive as the heat had been, it was now even more oppressive.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_218'>
The ringing of the big bell aroused him.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_219'>
At first he puzzled over something untoward he was sure had happened.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_220'>
A dead man is of no use on a plantation.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_221'>
I don't know why you're here at all.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_222'>
What part of the United States is your home.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_223'>
My, I'm almost homesick for it already.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_224'>
She nodded, and her eyes grew soft and moist.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_225'>
I was brought up the way most girls in Hawaii are brought up.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_226'>
That came before my A B C's.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_227'>
It was the same way with our revolvers and rifles.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_228'>
But it contributed to the smash.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_229'>
The last one I knew was an overseer.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_230'>
Do you know any good land around here.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_231'>
The Resident Commissioner is away in Australia.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_232'>
I cannot follow you, she said.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_233'>
I never allow what can't be changed to annoy me.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_234'>
Why, the average review is more nauseating than cod liver oil.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_235'>
His voice was passionately rebellious.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_236'>
Don't you see I hate you.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_237'>
So Hughie and I did the managing ourselves.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_238'>
It happened to him at the Gallina Society in Oakland one afternoon.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_239'>
He cried in such genuine dismay that she broke into hearty laughter.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_240'>
Wash your hands of me.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_241'>
I think it's much nicer to quarrel.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_242'>
I saw it when she rolled.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_243'>
I only read the quotations.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_244'>
He was the soul of devotion to his employers.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_245'>
Out of his eighteen hundred, he laid aside sixteen hundred each year.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_246'>
You have heard always how he was the lover of the Princess Naomi.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_247'>
They ought to pass here some time today.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_248'>
I had been sad too long already.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_249'>
All eyes, however, were staring at him in certitude of expectancy.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_250'>
He had observed the business life of Hawaii and developed a vaulting ambition.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_251'>
I may manage to freight a cargo back as well.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_252'>
O'Brien had been a clean living young man with ideals.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_253'>
He it was that lived to found the family of the Patino.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_254'>
Straight out they swam, their heads growing smaller and smaller.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_255'>
You won't die of malnutrition, be sure of that.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_256'>
See the length of the body and that elongated neck.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_257'>
They are coming ashore, whoever they are.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_258'>
Soaked in seawater they offset the heat rays.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_259'>
Think of investing in such an adventure.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_260'>
Nobody knew his history, they of the Junta least of all.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_261'>
I have been doubly baptized.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_262'>
They wouldn't be sweeping a big vessel like the Martha.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_263'>
Joan looked triumphantly at Sheldon, who bowed.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_264'>
And I hope you've got plenty of chain out, Captain Young.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_265'>
The discovery seemed to have been made on the spur of the moment.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_266'>
They handled two men already, both grub-thieves.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_267'>
Eli Harding asked, as Shunk started to follow.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_268'>
Now go ahead and tell me in a straightforward way what has happened.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_269'>
That's where they cut off the Scottish Chiefs and killed all hands.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_270'>
And after the bath a shave would not be bad.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_271'>
Now please give a plain statement of what occurred.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_272'>
You can take a vacation on pay.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_273'>
They are big trees and require plenty of room.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_274'>
And Raoul listened again to the tale of the house.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_275'>
There are no kiddies and half grown youths among them.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_276'>
Oolong Atoll was one hundred and forty miles in circumference.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_277'>
McCoy found a stifling, poisonous atmosphere in the pent cabin.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_278'>
It would give me nervous prostration.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_279'>
She said with chattering teeth.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_280'>
I'll be out of my head in fifteen minutes.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_281'>
I do not blame you for anything; remember that.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_282'>
If you mean to insinuate, Brentwood began hotly.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_283'>
The woman in you is only incidental, accidental, and irrelevant.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_284'>
There was no forecasting this strange girl's processes.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_285'>
But what they want with your toothbrush is more than I can imagine.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_286'>
Give them their choice between a fine or an official whipping.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_287'>
Keep an eye on him.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_288'>
Those are my oysters, he said at last.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_289'>
They are not regular oyster pirates, Nicholas continued.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_290'>
One by one the boys were captured.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_291'>
The weeks had gone by, and no overt acts had been attempted.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_292'>
Here, in the midmorning, the first casualty occurred.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_293'>
They were deep in the primeval forest.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_294'>
He had been foiled in his attempt to escape.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_295'>
And twenty men could hold it with spears and arrows.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_296'>
Bassett was a fastidious man.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_297'>
There's a big English general right now whose name is Roberts.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_298'>
This tacit promise of continued acquaintance gave Saxon a little joy-thrill.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_299'>
I tell you I am disgusted with this adventure tomfoolery and rot.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_300'>
From my earliest recollection my sleep was a period of terror.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_301'>
But all my dreams violated this law.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_302'>
It is very plausible to such people, a most convincing hypothesis.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_303'>
But they make the mistake of ignoring their own duality.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_304'>
I graduated last of my class.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_305'>
They had no fixed values, to be altered by adjectives and adverbs.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_306'>
He was pressing beyond the limits of his vocabulary.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_307'>
Very early in my life, I separated from my mother.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_308'>
His infernal chattering worries me even now as I think of it.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_309'>
White Leghorns, said  Missus Mortimer.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_310'>
Massage under tension, was the cryptic reply.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_311'>
Therefore, hurrah for the game.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_312'>
It lived in perpetual apprehension of that quarter of the compass.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_313'>
Broken-Tooth yelled with fright and pain.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_314'>
Thus was momentum gained in the Younger World.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_315'>
Saxon waited, for she knew a fresh idea had struck Billy.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_316'>
We had been chased by them ourselves, more than once.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_317'>
He was a wise hyena.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_318'>
Production is doubling and quadrupling upon itself.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_319'>
And the Edinburgh Evening News says, with editorial gloom.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_320'>
With my strength I slammed it full into Red-Eye's face.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_321'>
The log on which Lop-Ear was lying got adrift.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_322'>
This is a common experience with all of us.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_323'>
He considered the victory already his and stepped forward to the meat.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_324'>
It was not Red-Eye's way to forego revenge so easily.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_325'>
Whiz-zip-bang. Lop-Ear screamed with sudden anguish.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_326'>
Cherokee identified himself with his instinct.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_327'>
They were less stooped than we, less springy in their movements.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_328'>
The Fire People, like ourselves, lived in caves.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_329'>
Ah, indeed.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_330'>
Red-Eye never committed a more outrageous deed.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_331'>
Poor little Crooked-Leg was terribly scared.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_332'>
Unconsciously, our yells and exclamations yielded to this rhythm.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_333'>
This is no place for you.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_334'>
He'll knock you off a few sticks in no time.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_335'>
Red-Eye swung back and forth on the branch farther down.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_336'>
So unexpected was my charge that I knocked him off his feet.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_337'>
Encouraged by my conduct, Big-Face became a sudden ally.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_338'>
The fighting had now become intermittent.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_339'>
They obeyed him, and went here and there at his commands.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_340'>
It was like the beating of hoofs.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_341'>
Why, doggone you all, shake again.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_342'>
Seventeen, no, eighteen days ago.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_343'>
You mean for this State, General, Alberta.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_344'>
He seemed to fill it with his tremendous vitality.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_345'>
She was trying to pass the apron string around him.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_346'>
Get down and dig in.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_347'>
They are greatly delighted with anything that is bright or giveth a sound.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_348'>
They only lifted seven hundred and fifty.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_349'>
It was simple, in its way, and no virtue of his.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_350'>
Is that Pat Hanrahan's mug looking hungry and willing.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_351'>
It was more like sugar.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_352'>
I'm sure going along with you all, Elijah.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_353'>
Here the explosion of mirth drowned him out.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_354'>
Fresh meat they failed to obtain.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_355'>
A burst of laughter was his reward.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_356'>
You don't catch me at any such foolishness.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_357'>
A month passed by, and Bonanza Creek remained quiet.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_358'>
They continued valiantly to lie, but the truth continued to outrun them.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_359'>
Earth and gravel seemed to fill the pan.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_360'>
But he no longer cared quite so much for that form of diversion.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_361'>
But he did not broach it, preferring to mature it carefully.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_362'>
Nope, not the slightest idea.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_363'>
It is not an attempt to smash the market.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_364'>
We have plenty of capital ourselves, and yet we want more.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_365'>
These rumors may even originate with us.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_366'>
A wildly exciting time was his during the week preceding Thursday the eighteenth.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_367'>
There is not an iota of truth in it, certainly not.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_368'>
I just do appreciate it without being able to express my feelings.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_369'>
In partnership with Daylight, the pair raided the San Jose Interurban.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_370'>
He saw all men in the business game doing this.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_371'>
It issued a rate of forty two dollars a car on charcoal.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_372'>
He saw only the effect in a general, sketchy way.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_373'>
Points of view, new ideas, life.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_374'>
But life's worth more than cash, she argued.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_375'>
The butchers and meat cutters refused to handle meat destined for unfair restaurants.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_376'>
Your price, my son, is just about thirty per week.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_377'>
This sound did not disturb the hush and awe of the place.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_378'>
That's why its boundaries are all gouged and jagged.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_379'>
How old are you, daddy.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_380'>
But in the canyons water was plentiful and also a luxuriant forest growth.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_381'>
My name's Ferguson.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_382'>
Daylight found himself charmed and made curious by the little man.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_383'>
To his surprise, her answer was flat and uncompromising.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_384'>
The farmer works the soil and produces grain.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_385'>
That's what Carnegie did.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_386'>
I can't argue with you, and you know that.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_387'>
Bob, growing disgusted, turned back suddenly and attempted to pass Mab.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_388'>
It was my idea to a tee.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_389'>
Mab, she said.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_390'>
I'll go over tomorrow afternoon.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_391'>
But he reconciled himself to it by an act of faith.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_392'>
There is that magnificent Bob, eating his head off in the stable.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_393'>
Already he had begun borrowing from the banks.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_394'>
It's the strap hangers that'll keep us from going under.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_395'>
As for himself, weren't the street railway earnings increasing steadily.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_396'>
A rising tide of fat had submerged them.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_397'>
Call me that again, he murmured ecstatically.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_398'>
In the car were Unwin and Harrison, while Jones sat with the chauffeur.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_399'>
And here's another idea.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_400'>
Manuel had one besetting sin.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_401'>
The man smiled grimly, and brought a hatchet and a club.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_402'>
Curly rushed her antagonist, who struck again and leaped aside.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_403'>
His newborn cunning gave him poise and control.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_404'>
Perrault found one with head buried in the grub box.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_405'>
It seemed the ordained order of things that dogs should work.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_406'>
And that was the last of Francois and Perrault.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_407'>
Mercedes screamed, cried, laughed, and manifested the chaotic abandonment of hysteria.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_408'>
The Eldorado emptied its occupants into the street to see the test.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_409'>
He could feel a new stir in the land.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_410'>
So we have to fit the boat throughout with oil lamps as well.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_411'>
It will break our hearts and our backs to hoist anchor by hand.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_412'>
There is another virtue in these bulkheads.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_413'>
But I am at the end of my resources.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_414'>
Now our figuring was all right.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_415'>
It lasted as a deterrent for two days.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_416'>
The added weight had a velocity of fifteen miles per hour.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_417'>
It is also an insidious, deceitful sun.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_418'>
The Portuguese boy crawled nearer and nearer.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_419'>
The Portuguese boy passed the Hawaiian.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_420'>
When I came to I was waving my hat and murmuring ecstatically.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_421'>
By golly, the boy wins.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_422'>
Halfway around the track one donkey got into an argument with its rider.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_423'>
McVeigh when he returns from a trip to Honolulu.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_424'>
Obviously, it was a disease that could be contracted by contact.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_425'>
Otherwise no restriction is put upon their seafaring.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_426'>
They do not know the length of time of incubation.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_427'>
Enters now the psychology of the situation.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_428'>
It was not exactly a deportation.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_429'>
Quick was the disappointment in his face, yet smiling was the acquiescence.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_430'>
Nevertheless we found ourselves once more in the high seat of abundance.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_431'>
Wada and Nakata were in a bit of a funk.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_432'>
The boy at the wheel lost his head.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_433'>
To her the bridge was tambo, which is the native for taboo.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_434'>
A half a case of tobacco was worth three pounds.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_435'>
What do you mean by this outrageous conduct.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_436'>
But Martin smiled a superior smile.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_437'>
By that answer my professional medical prestige stood or fell.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_438'>
At sea, Monday, March sixteenth, nineteen oh eight.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_439'>
At sea, Wednesday, March eighteenth, nineteen oh eight.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_440'>
Yes, sir, I corrected.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_441'>
Violent life and athletic sports had never appealed to me.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_442'>
You live on an income which your father earned.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_443'>
He was worth nothing to the world.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_444'>
Then you don't believe in altruism.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_445'>
The creative joy, I murmured.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_446'>
He deluged me, overwhelmed me with argument.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_447'>
Ah, it is growing dark and darker.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_448'>
I was Hump, cabin boy on the schooner Ghost.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_449'>
A sinewy hand, dripping with water, was clutching the rail.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_450'>
No man ate of the seal meat or the oil.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_451'>
I noticed blood spouting from Kerfoot's left hand.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_452'>
Three oilers and a fourth engineer, was his greeting.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_453'>
Eighteen hundred, he calculated.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_454'>
The sharp voice of Wolf Larsen aroused me.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_455'>
I obeyed, and a minute or two later they stood before him.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_456'>
But it won't continue, she said with easy confidence.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_457'>
What I saw I could not at first believe.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_458'>
The stout wood was crushed like an eggshell.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_459'>
There's too much of the schoolboy in me.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_460'>
I had forgotten their existence.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_461'>
Ah, we were very close together in that moment.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_462'>
But she swung obediently on her heel into the wind.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_463'>
They are his tongue, by which he makes his knowledge articulate.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_464'>
Between the rush of the cascades, streaks of rust showed everywhere.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_465'>
He'll never do a tap of work the whole Voyage.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_466'>
Captain West may be a Samurai, but he is also human.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_467'>
And so early in the voyage, too.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_468'>
In the matter of curry she is a sheer genius.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_469'>
The eastern heavens were equally spectacular.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_470'>
He spat it out like so much venom.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_471'>
I saw  Mister Pike nod his head grimly and sarcastically.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_472'>
He is too keenly intelligent, too sharply sensitive, successfully to endure.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_473'>
The night was calm and snowy.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_474'>
I sailed third mate in the little Vampire before you were born.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_475'>
His outstretched arm dropped to his side, and he paused.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_476'>
At this moment I felt a stir at my shoulder.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_477'>
Wada, Louis, and the steward are servants of Asiatic breed.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_478'>
Also, she has forbidden them smoking their pipes in the after-room.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_479'>
I tried to read George Moore last night, and was dreadfully bored.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_480'>
Tom Spink has a harpoon.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_481'>
Nimrod replied, with a slight manifestation of sensitiveness.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_482'>
And their chief virtue lies in that they will never wear out.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_483'>
Beyond dispute, Corry Hutchinson had married Mabel Holmes.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_484'>
No-sir-ee.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_485'>
Each insult added to the value of the claim.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_486'>
For the rest, he was a mere automaton.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_487'>
The river bared its bosom, and snorting steamboats challenged the wilderness.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_488'>
Their love burned with increasing brightness.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_489'>
They were artists, not biologists.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_490'>
Both Johnny and his mother shuffled their feet as they walked.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_491'>
And as in denial of guilt, the one-legged boy replied.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_492'>
Burnt out like the crater of a volcano.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_493'>
The boy, O'Brien, was specially maltreated.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_494'>
O'Brien took off his coat and bared his right arm.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_495'>
He bore no grudges and had few enemies.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_496'>
And Tom King patiently endured.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_497'>
King took every advantage he knew.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_498'>
The lines were now very taut.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_499'>
And right there I saw and knew it all.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_500'>
Who the devil gave it to you to be judge and jury.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_501'>
You're joking me, sir, the other managed to articulate.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_502'>
Anything unusual or abnormal was sufficient to send a fellow to Molokai.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_503'>
His beady black eyes saw bargains where other men saw bankruptcy.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_504'>
He was an athlete and a giant.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_505'>
We fished sharks on Niihau together.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_506'>
The Claudine was leaving next morning for Honolulu.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_507'>
In short, my joyous individualism was dominated by the orthodox bourgeois ethics.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_508'>
Soon shall it be thrust back from off prostrate humanity.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_509'>
Yet, in accordance with Ernest's test of truth, it worked.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_510'>
Much more Ernest told them of themselves and of his disillusionment.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_511'>
There is more behind this than a mere university ideal.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_512'>
No, it is a palace, wherein there are many servants.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_513'>
We must give ourselves and not our money alone.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_514'>
We are consumed in our own flesh-pots.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_515'>
But here amongst ourselves let us speak out.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_516'>
Also, there was awe in their faces.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_517'>
Out of abstractions Ernest had conjured a vision and made them see it.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_518'>
Illuminating oil was becoming all profit.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_519'>
Such an act was in direct violation of the laws of the land.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_520'>
He was fond of quoting a fragment from a certain poem.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_521'>
Without them he could not run his empire.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_522'>
For such countries nothing remained but reorganization.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_523'>
They could not continue their method of producing surpluses.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_524'>
At once would be instituted a dozen cooperative commonwealth states.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_525'>
The Oligarchy wanted violence, and it set its agents provocateurs to work.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_526'>
Nowhere did the raw earth appear.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_527'>
The lush vegetation of that sheltered spot make a natural shield.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_528'>
Men who endure it, call it living death.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_529'>
As I say, he had tapped the message very rapidly.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_530'>
Ask him, I laughed, then turned to Pasquini.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_531'>
In what bucolic school of fence he had been taught was beyond imagining.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_532'>
May drought destroy your crops.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_533'>
Dunham, can your boy go along with Jesse.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_534'>
But Johannes could, and did.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_535'>
A new preacher and a new doctrine come to Jerusalem.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_536'>
He would destroy all things that are fixed.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_537'>
He was an enthusiast and a desert dweller.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_538'>
What Pascal glimpsed with the vision of a seer, I have lived.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_539'>
I should like to engage just for one whole life in that.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_540'>
Yea, so are all the lesser animals of today clean.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_541'>
The Warden with a quart of champagne.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_542'>
Without a doubt, some of them have dinner engagements.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_543'>
I had been born with no organic, chemical predisposition toward alcohol.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_544'>
He may anticipate the day of his death.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_545'>
The Italian rancho was a bachelor establishment.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_546'>
I lost my balance and pitched head foremost into the ooze.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_547'>
Men like Joe Goose dated existence from drunk to drunk.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_548'>
Also, churches and preachers I had never known.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_549'>
Do you know that we weigh every pound of coal we burn.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_550'>
This also became part of the daily schedule.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_551'>
All an appearance can know is mirage.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_552'>
Yet he dreams he is immortal, I argue feebly.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_553'>
I am writing these lines in Honolulu, Hawaii.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_554'>
Jack London, Waikiki Beach, Honolulu, Oahu.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_555'>
Jerry was so secure in his nook that he did not roll away.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_556'>
Why, he's bought forty pounds of goods from you already.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_557'>
The last refugee had passed.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_558'>
And the foundation stone of service, in his case, was obedience.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_559'>
Peace be unto you and grace before the Lord.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_560'>
His mouth opened; words shaped vainly on his lips.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_561'>
Bill lingered, contemplating his work with artistic appreciation.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_562'>
What the flaming.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_563'>
 Missus McFee's jaws brought together with a snap.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_564'>
Then it is as I said, Womble announced with finality.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_565'>
With them were Indians, also three other men.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_566'>
Dennin's hands were released long enough for him to sign the document.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_567'>
Now Irvine was a man of impulse, a poet.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_568'>
He was just bursting with joy, joy over what.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_569'>
At Lake Linderman I had one canoe, very good Peterborough canoe.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_570'>
Behind him lay the thousand-years-long road across all Siberia and Russia.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_571'>
He had forgotten to build a fire and thaw out.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_572'>
I never saw anything like her in my life.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_573'>
There was no law on the Yukon save what they made for themselves.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_574'>
Good business man, Curly, O'Brien was saying.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_575'>
There weren't any missions, and he was the man to know.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_576'>
And the big Persian knew of his existence before he did of hers.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_577'>
Once the jews harp began emitting its barbaric rhythms, Michael was helpless.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_578'>
But we'll just postpone this.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_579'>
There was the Emma Louisa.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_580'>
This is my fifth voyage.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_581'>
It was this proposition that started the big idea in Daughtry's mind.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_582'>
Daughtry elaborated on the counting trick by bringing Cocky along.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_583'>
Enjoy it he did, but principally for Steward's sake.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_584'>
I have long noted your thirst unquenchable.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_585'>
Wonder if he's a lion dog, Charles suggested.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_586'>
We don't see ourselves as foolish.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_587'>
He had comparatively no advantages at first.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_588'>
He had proved it today, with his amateurish and sophomoric productions.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_589'>
I was sick once, typhoid.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_590'>
In a way he is my protege.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_591'>
We are both children together.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_592'>
It's only his indigestion I find fault with.
</fileid>
<fileid id='a0001_593'>
She'd make a good wife for the cashier.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_001'>
Gad, do I remember it.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_002'>
You got out by fighting, and I through a pretty girl.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_003'>
I can see that knife now.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_004'>
When I can't see beauty in woman I want to die.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_005'>
His slim fingers closed like steel about Philip's.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_006'>
He seized Gregson by the arm and led him to the door.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_007'>
Hear the Indian dogs wailing down at Churchill.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_008'>
Burke himself had criticized it because of the smile.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_009'>
I'd say there was going to be a glorious scrap.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_010'>
He turned the map to Gregson, pointing with his finger.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_011'>
His eyes never took themselves for an instant from his companion's face.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_012'>
Something that Whittemore had not yet said thrilled him.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_013'>
Lakes and rivers, hundreds of them, thousands of them.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_014'>
Whitefish, Gregson, whitefish and trout.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_015'>
They robbed me a few years later.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_016'>
He chuckled as he pulled out his pipe and began filling it.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_017'>
Everything was working smoothly, better than I had expected.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_018'>
I was completely lost in my work.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_019'>
His slim hands gripped the edges of the table.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_020'>
He made no reply as he waited for Whittemore to continue.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_021'>
Philip dropped back into his chair.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_022'>
If I was out of the game it would be easily made.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_023'>
MacDougall, my engineer, believes it.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_024'>
It is growing, every day, every hour.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_025'>
Now, you understand.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_026'>
You have associated with some of these men.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_027'>
And there's no chivalry, no quarter shown in this fight.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_028'>
Lord Fitzhugh is the key to the whole situation.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_029'>
All operations have been carried on from Montreal and Toronto.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_030'>
Gregson held a lighted match until it burnt his fingertips.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_031'>
Gregson had seated himself under the lamp and was sharpening a pencil.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_032'>
He caught himself with a jerk.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_033'>
How does your wager look now.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_034'>
He confessed that the sketch had startled him.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_035'>
After all, the picture was only a resemblance.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_036'>
He wondered, too, where Roscoe was.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_037'>
Philip knew that she was not an Indian.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_038'>
In her haste to get away she had forgotten these things.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_039'>
Philip took a step toward Gregson, half determined to awaken him.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_040'>
The thought set his blood tingling.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_041'>
But if Pierre did not return, until tomorrow.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_042'>
Ten minutes had not elapsed since he had dropped the handkerchief.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_043'>
It won't be for sale.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_044'>
For a few moments he ate in silence.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_045'>
Philip did not pursue the subject.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_046'>
Philip produced a couple of cigars and took a chair opposite him.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_047'>
Suppose you saw me at work through the window.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_048'>
He looked like one who had passed through an uncomfortable hour or two.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_049'>
There was nothing more, except a large ink blot under the words.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_050'>
All this day Gregson remained in the cabin.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_051'>
The sixth day he spent in the cabin with Gregson.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_052'>
The flush was gone from her face.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_053'>
That is why I am, am rattled, he laughed.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_054'>
He understood the meaning of the look.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_055'>
She was even more beautiful than when I saw her, before.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_056'>
I'll give a thousand if you produce her, retorted Gregson.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_057'>
They have won popular sentiment through the newspapers.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_058'>
We must achieve our own salvation.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_059'>
In moments of mental energy Philip was restless.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_060'>
He would keep his faith with Gregson for the promised day or two.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_061'>
Something about it seemed to fascinate him, to challenge his presence.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_062'>
Now it was missing from the wall.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_063'>
He boiled himself some coffee and sat down to wait.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_064'>
I'm going down there with you, and I'm going to fight.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_065'>
Now have you got anything to say against me,  Mister Philip.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_066'>
If I meet her again I shall apologize, said Eileen.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_067'>
Below him the shadow was broken into a pool of rippling starlight.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_068'>
Only the chance sound had led him to observe them.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_069'>
Could the incident have anything to do with Jeanne and Pierre.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_070'>
There was no chance to fire without hitting him.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_071'>
There was no answer from the other side.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_072'>
Then he hastened on, as Pierre had guided him.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_073'>
With these arguments he convinced himself that he should go on alone.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_074'>
Yet, behind them there was another and more powerful motive.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_075'>
In that case he could not miss them, if he used caution.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_076'>
Before Philip could recover himself Jeanne's startled guards were upon him.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_077'>
It is the nearest refuge.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_078'>
There was pride and strength, the ring of triumph in his voice.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_079'>
The truth of it set Jeanne quivering.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_080'>
Tomorrow it will be strong enough for you to stand upon.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_081'>
You were going to leave after you saw me on the rock.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_082'>
He bit his tongue, and cursed himself at this fresh break.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_083'>
In it there was something that was almost tragedy.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_084'>
Your face is red with blood.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_085'>
Her eyes smiled truth at him as he came up the bank.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_086'>
He can care for himself.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_087'>
They will search for us between their camp and Churchill.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_088'>
Until I die, he exclaimed.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_089'>
Her beautiful hair was done up in shining coils.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_090'>
The Churchill narrowed and its current became swifter as they progressed.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_091'>
For a full half minute Jeanne looked at him without speaking.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_092'>
I want to die in it.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_093'>
Darkness hid him from Jeanne.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_094'>
And yet if she came he had no words to say.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_095'>
He heard a sound which brought him quickly into consciousness of day.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_096'>
Within himself he called it no longer his own.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_097'>
Besides, that noise makes me deaf.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_098'>
Philip looked back from the crest and saw Jeanne leaning over the canoe.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_099'>
Fifty yards ahead of her were the first of the rocks.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_100'>
There was one chance, and only one, of saving Jeanne.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_101'>
You're a devil for fighting, and will surely win.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_102'>
I'll only be in the way.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_103'>
He lifted his eyes, and a strange cry burst from his lips.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_104'>
Shooting pains passed like flashes of electricity through his body.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_105'>
I know that you are in charge there, and Jeanne knows.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_106'>
For a full minute the two men stared into each other's face.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_107'>
He was sure, now, of but few things.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_108'>
It was a miracle, and I owe you my life.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_109'>
Philip ate lightly of the food which Pierre had ready for him.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_110'>
Such men believe, when they come together.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_111'>
The journey was continued at dawn.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_112'>
Jeanne and Pierre both gazed toward the great rock.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_113'>
There was something pathetic in the girl's attitude now.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_114'>
He moved his position, and the illusion was gone.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_115'>
For two hours not a word passed between them.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_116'>
I have hunted along this ridge, replied Philip.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_117'>
That's Thorpe's, said the young engineer.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_118'>
We saw your light, and thought you wouldn't mind a call.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_119'>
Billinger may arrive in time.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_120'>
There's the hitch, replied Thorpe, rolling a cigarette.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_121'>
I want my men to work by themselves.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_122'>
Philip saw MacDougall soon after his short talk with Thorpe.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_123'>
Neither could they understand the growing disaffection among Thorpe's men.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_124'>
Two weeks passed, and in that time Thorpe left camp three times.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_125'>
It was the third or fourth time that Philip had heard MacDougall swear.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_126'>
Blood was oozing slowly from the wounded man's right breast.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_127'>
He destroyed everything that had belonged to the woman.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_128'>
Philip bent low over Pierre.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_129'>
Did Thorpe go to see any one in Churchill.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_130'>
She saw the answer in his face.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_131'>
Thorpe and his men were to destroy this camp, and kill you.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_132'>
There is no need of further detail, now, for you can understand.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_133'>
There followed a roar that shook the earth.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_134'>
Blind with rage, he darted in.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_135'>
In it was the joy of life.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_136'>
Swiftly his eyes measured the situation.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_137'>
But this little defect did not worry him.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_138'>
And then, steadily, he began to chew.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_139'>
Together they ate the rabbit.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_140'>
They edged nearer, and stood shoulder to shoulder facing their world.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_141'>
It was beating and waiting in the ambush of those black pits.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_142'>
Something vastly more thrilling had come into it now.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_143'>
It took him half an hour to reach the edge of it.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_144'>
But there was no longer the mother yearning in his heart.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_145'>
Besides, had he not whipped the big owl in the forest.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_146'>
After all, it was simply a mistake in judgment.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_147'>
Had it struck squarely it would have killed him.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_148'>
The Indian even poked his stick into the thick ground spruce.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_149'>
Pebbles and dirt flew along with hair and fur.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_150'>
And he was filled with a strange and foreboding fear.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_151'>
It was steel, a fisher trap.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_152'>
OW, a wild dog, he growled.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_153'>
He was a pariah; a wanderer without a friend or a home.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_154'>
That is the strange part of it.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_155'>
His freshly caught furs he flung to the floor.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_156'>
For that reason Le Beau had chosen him to fight the big fight.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_157'>
In the crib the baby sat up and began to prattle.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_158'>
She obeyed, shrinking back with the baby in her arms.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_159'>
His teeth shut with a last click.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_160'>
It was over when he made his way through the ring of spectators.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_161'>
In a flash he was on his feet, facing him.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_162'>
He thought he saw a shudder pass through the Factor's shoulders.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_163'>
The moon had already begun its westward decline.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_164'>
They laughed like two happy children.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_165'>
He pulled, and the log crashed down to break his back.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_166'>
Fast, but endure.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_167'>
A little before dawn of the day following, the fire relief came.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_168'>
The Indian felt the worship of her warm in his heart.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_169'>
He drew in a deep breath as he looked at them.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_170'>
Then he shouted, Shut up.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_171'>
He changed his seat for a steamer reclining chair.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_172'>
On the far corner of the compound fence a hawk brooded.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_173'>
To these he gave castor oil.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_174'>
Hatred and murder and lust for revenge they possessed to overflowing.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_175'>
Sheldon glanced at the thermometer.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_176'>
I'll see to poor Hughie.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_177'>
Her gray eyes were flashing, and her lips were quivering.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_178'>
Also, I want information.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_179'>
Let them go out and eat with my boys.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_180'>
I, I beg pardon, he drawled.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_181'>
And you preferred a cannibal isle and a cartridge belt.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_182'>
I was in New York when the crash came.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_183'>
No, I did not fall among thieves.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_184'>
Such things in her brain were like so many oaths on her lips.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_185'>
Your being wrecked here has been a godsend to me.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_186'>
I can't go elsewhere, by your own account.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_187'>
Her achievements with cocoanuts were a revelation.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_188'>
He glanced down at her helplessly, and moistened his lips.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_189'>
That is what distinguishes all of us from the lower animals.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_190'>
Idealism led him to philosophic anarchy, and his family threw him off.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_191'>
He also contended that better confidence was established by carrying no weapons.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_192'>
Outsiders are allowed five minute speeches, the sick man urged.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_193'>
So was Packard's finish suicide.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_194'>
Joan cried, with shining eyes.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_195'>
Nobody knows how the natives got them.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_196'>
How can you manage all alone,  Mister Young.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_197'>
The planters are already considering the matter.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_198'>
I use great trouble advisedly.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_199'>
Dear Sir, Your second victim has fallen on schedule time.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_200'>
We leave the eventuality to time and law.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_201'>
I also understand that similar branch organizations have made their appearance in Europe.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_202'>
Society is shaken to its foundations.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_203'>
A month in Australia would finish me.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_204'>
Down through the perfume weighted air fluttered the snowy fluffs of the cottonwoods.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_205'>
You were destroying my life.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_206'>
Horses and rifles had been her toys, camp and trail her nursery.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_207'>
I'm as good as a man, she urged.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_208'>
You read the quotations in today's paper.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_209'>
He's terribly touchy about his black wards, as he calls them.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_210'>
Whatever he guessed he locked away in the taboo room of Naomi.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_211'>
This is eighteen eighty.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_212'>
Death is and has been ever since old Maui died.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_213'>
Some boy, she laughed acquiescence.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_214'>
Let us talk it over and find a way out.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_215'>
It is a good property, and worth more than that.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_216'>
I wish you were more adaptable, Joan retorted.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_217'>
Such is my passage engaged on the steamer.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_218'>
The issue was not in doubt.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_219'>
Well, there are better men in Hawaii, that's all.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_220'>
Harry Bancroft, Dave lied.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_221'>
It's a Yankee, Joan cried.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_222'>
He was the leader, and Tudor was his lieutenant.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_223'>
They likewise are disinclined to being eaten.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_224'>
But to culture the Revolution thus far had exhausted the Junta.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_225'>
The President of the United States was his friend.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_226'>
Your face was the personification of duplicity.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_227'>
Shorty turned to their employers.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_228'>
You were engaged.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_229'>
I saw it all myself, and it was splendid.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_230'>
Now run along, and tell them to hurry.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_231'>
What's that grub-thief got to do with it.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_232'>
It was a superb picture.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_233'>
So she said, the irate skipper dashed on.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_234'>
And watch out for wet feet, was his parting advice.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_235'>
Raoul yelled, in order to make himself heard.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_236'>
Oolong was two hundred and fifty miles from the nearest land.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_237'>
They just lay off in the bush and plugged away.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_238'>
The very thought of the effort to swim over was nauseating.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_239'>
And there was a dog that barked.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_240'>
There are four, all low, McCoy answered.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_241'>
The women they carried away with them to the Big Valley.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_242'>
The Japanese understood as we could never school ourselves or hope to understand.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_243'>
They had been on the same lay as ourselves.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_244'>
You are positively soulless, he said savagely.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_245'>
Harrison is still my chauffeur.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_246'>
The boy grew and prospered.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_247'>
He wanted to give the finish to this foe already so far gone.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_248'>
Exciting times are the lot of the fish patrol.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_249'>
I know they are my oysters.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_250'>
By this time Charley was as enraged as the Greek.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_251'>
They must have been swept away by the chaotic currents.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_252'>
It resembled tea less than lager beer resembles champagne.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_253'>
The very opposite is true; they are discouraged vagabonds.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_254'>
At the same time spears and arrows began to fall among the invaders.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_255'>
Then, again, Tudor had such an irritating way about him.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_256'>
Outwardly, he maintained a calm and smiling aspect.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_257'>
Tudor surveyed him with withering disgust.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_258'>
You fired me out of your house, in short.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_259'>
Her mouth opened, but instead of speaking she drew a long sigh.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_260'>
It's worth eight dollars.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_261'>
And he did hurt my arm.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_262'>
Saxon's onto her job.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_263'>
Only once did I confide the strangeness of it all to another.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_264'>
But this time it was Saxon who rebelled.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_265'>
I was not to cry out in the face of fear.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_266'>
And now put yourself in my place for a moment.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_267'>
The boy threw back his head with pride.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_268'>
Saxon nodded, and the boy frowned.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_269'>
Why not like any railroad station or ferry depot.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_270'>
We could throw stones with our feet.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_271'>
It was put together in a casual, helter-skelter sort of way.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_272'>
These were merely stout sticks an inch or so in diameter.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_273'>
Then it was that a strange thing happened.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_274'>
From the source of light a harsh voice said.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_275'>
But I did not enjoy it long.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_276'>
We were now good friends.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_277'>
Two of the Folk were already up.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_278'>
Now animals do not like mockery.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_279'>
He gave one last snarl and slid from view among the trees.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_280'>
Again the girls applauded, and  Missus Hall cried.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_281'>
Just the same I'd sooner be myself than have book indigestion.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_282'>
Some of the smaller veins had doubtless been ruptured.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_283'>
But we were without this momentum.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_284'>
There was one difficulty, however.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_285'>
The hyena proceeded to dine.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_286'>
The time was considered auspicious.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_287'>
Or have they already devised one.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_288'>
We would not spend another such night.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_289'>
At first his progress was slow and erratic.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_290'>
He placed his paw on one, and its movements were accelerated.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_291'>
The awe of man rushed over him again.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_292'>
The Fire-Men wore animal skins around their waists and across their shoulders.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_293'>
Between him and all domestic animals there must be no hostilities.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_294'>
For a much longer time Lop-Ear and I remained and watched.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_295'>
All right, Sir, replied Jock with great regret.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_296'>
At times I wondered where Sir Archibald got his style.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_297'>
Why should a fellow throw up the sponge after the first round.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_298'>
His hand shot out and clutched Crooked-Leg by the neck.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_299'>
Miss Brodie's smile was slightly sarcastic.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_300'>
Does the old boy often go off at half-cock that way.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_301'>
A flying arrow passed between us.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_302'>
I pulled, suddenly, with all my might.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_303'>
Here we allow our solicitors to look after our legal work.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_304'>
His previous wives had never lived long enough to bear him children.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_305'>
It was our river emerging like ourselves from the great swamp.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_306'>
Cameron looked at his hands with their long, sinewy fingers.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_307'>
We got few vegetables and fruits, and became fish eaters.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_308'>
We never made another migration.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_309'>
Nor was Elam Harnish an exception.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_310'>
A little treatment, massage, with some help from the doctor.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_311'>
The twenty ninthvery foggy.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_312'>
Dig in; you're sure good, was Daylight's answer.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_313'>
The apron string loomed near and he shied like an unbroken colt.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_314'>
He had been born with this endowment.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_315'>
And this was their sole conversation throughout the meal.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_316'>
Though the aurora still flamed, another day had begun.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_317'>
He did not believe in the burning of daylight for such a luxury.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_318'>
Again he had done the big thing.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_319'>
Daylight was tired, profoundly tired.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_320'>
The regret in his voice was provocative of a second burst of laughter.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_321'>
Instead, he arrived on the night of the second day.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_322'>
Their supply of grub was gone.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_323'>
Crickets began to chirp, and more geese and ducks flew overhead.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_324'>
Not till the twentieth of May did the river break.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_325'>
It was a gigantic inadequacy.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_326'>
Our  Mister Howison will call upon you at your hotel.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_327'>
He had been so easy.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_328'>
Change chairs, Daylight commanded.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_329'>
I'd sooner have my chips back.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_330'>
They only had a little thirty thousand dollar fire.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_331'>
His partners had starved and died on the Stewart.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_332'>
As to how she dressed, he had no ideas at all.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_333'>
It does, was her audacious answer.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_334'>
Oh, it's just a novel, a love story.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_335'>
Whoever lived on the ranch did that.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_336'>
How old are you, mother.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_337'>
Here he got a fresh thrill.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_338'>
It was unobtrusive, yet it was there.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_339'>
Well, I'll be plumb gosh darned.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_340'>
These quick little joys of hers were sources of joy to him.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_341'>
I play that choice wide open to win.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_342'>
Each improvement makes the value of everything else pump up.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_343'>
But how are you going to do it.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_344'>
Lots of men take women buggy riding.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_345'>
Daylight made no answer, and the door closed behind him.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_346'>
There's not an iota of truth in it.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_347'>
But ever his gaze returned to that Crouched Venus on the piano.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_348'>
Would you be satisfied with that one hundredth part of me.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_349'>
In such a tumbling of values was no time to sell.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_350'>
Stand off butcher and baker and all the rest.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_351'>
Matthewson, who's this bookkeeper, Rogers.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_352'>
Now just what do you want to know.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_353'>
I want to know how all this is possible.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_354'>
It's that much junk.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_355'>
There was proper division of labor in the work they individually performed.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_356'>
He loved to play Chinese lottery.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_357'>
The Law of Club and Fang
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_358'>
The temperature dropped to fifty below zero and remained there the whole trip.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_359'>
And as never before, he was ready to obey.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_360'>
This state of mind comes of an undue prominence of the ego.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_361'>
There are the canals of China, and the Yang-tse River.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_362'>
We threaten to be of the one mind before the voyage is completed.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_363'>
She was built primarily to sail.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_364'>
In the Bohemian Club of San Francisco there are some crack sailors.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_365'>
My age, in years, is twenty two.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_366'>
I forgot how easily I had taught myself from the printed page.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_367'>
Any average young fellow can teach himself in a week.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_368'>
Please do not think that I already know it all.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_369'>
You see, we were teaching ourselves.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_370'>
And now behold the perversity of things.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_371'>
Yield yourself to the waters that are ripping and tearing at you.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_372'>
 Mister McVeigh told me about him.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_373'>
Unlike Joshua, he stood in no need of divine assistance.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_374'>
To say the least, Captain Cook was a rather thorough going empiricist.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_375'>
Man could not conquer them.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_376'>
Thought I, and a worthy fool he proved.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_377'>
A scarlet loincloth completed his costume.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_378'>
I like to speculate upon the glorious future of man.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_379'>
Christmas is an easy problem compared with a Polynesian giving-feast.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_380'>
He had peeled off his shirt and was wildly waving it.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_381'>
And how would we ever find ourselves.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_382'>
I defy any man to get a Solomon Island sore in California.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_383'>
A bush chief had died a natural death.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_384'>
The skipper's and Nakata's gymnastics served as a translation without words.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_385'>
Last night he showed all the symptoms of coming down with pneumonia.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_386'>
My idea was that he would have more influence over the natives.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_387'>
It is merely the simple superlative.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_388'>
I made no more overtures.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_389'>
Among my minor afflictions, I may mention a new and mysterious one.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_390'>
The voyage was our idea of a good time.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_391'>
At sea, Tuesday, March seventeenth, nineteen oh eight.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_392'>
Yes, sir, he answered, with cheerful alacrity.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_393'>
I was still weak from my prolonged immersion.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_394'>
The boy hesitated, then mastered his temper.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_395'>
I was beneath the water, suffocating and drowning.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_396'>
The pain from my hurt knee was agonizing.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_397'>
The hunters were still arguing and roaring like some semi-human amphibious breed.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_398'>
I have been robbed, sir, I amended.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_399'>
You were looking squeamish this afternoon, he began.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_400'>
How could I answer the question on the spur of the moment.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_401'>
I learned it myself in English ships.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_402'>
An altruistic act is an act performed for the welfare of others.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_403'>
Knowing him, I review the old Scandinavian myths with clearer understanding.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_404'>
Yes, and no, sir, was the slow reply.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_405'>
And each year something happened, and I did not go.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_406'>
How in hell did he know it was you in the dark.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_407'>
Of course much grumbling went on, and little outbursts were continually occurring.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_408'>
You have all the advantage.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_409'>
The dirk mentioned by Wolf Larsen rested in its sheath on my hip.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_410'>
Have you ever earned a dollar by your own labour.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_411'>
He gave no reason, but his motive was obvious enough.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_412'>
Ah, it was sweet in my ears.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_413'>
He may desire to escape pain, or to enjoy pleasure.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_414'>
It was impossible to hoist sail and claw off that shore.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_415'>
There was nothing for us but the wide raw ocean.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_416'>
I arose obediently and went down the beach.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_417'>
The next thing to watch out for is bed sores.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_418'>
At that moment I got the impression that she was willowy.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_419'>
Your father's fifth command, he nodded.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_420'>
On occasion, on this traverse, the Cape Verde Islands are raised.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_421'>
She is essentially the life-giving, life-conserving female of the species.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_422'>
This was when the explosion occurred.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_423'>
Also, at regular intervals, he would mutter.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_424'>
It is a very tenable hypothesis, and will bear looking into.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_425'>
There were orange-green, gold-green, and a copper-green.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_426'>
The Gabriel voice of the Samurai rang out.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_427'>
The sunsets grow more bizarre and spectacular off this coast of the Argentine.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_428'>
The history of our westward-faring race is written in it.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_429'>
And the Eurasian Chinese-Englishman bowed himself away.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_430'>
They were babbling and chattering all together.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_431'>
Too much, he told me, with ominous rolling head.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_432'>
He is a candidate, rising from the serf class to our class.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_433'>
We are cooking on the coal stove and on the oil burners.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_434'>
The steward has just tendered me a respectful bit of advice.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_435'>
Well, did they eat.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_436'>
Famine had been my great ally.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_437'>
Nowhere in the North is the soil so prolific.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_438'>
They ran the canoe in and climbed the high earth bank.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_439'>
The land exchanged its austere robes for the garb of a smiling wanton.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_440'>
There were stir and bustle, new faces, and fresh facts.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_441'>
And there was Ethel Baird, whom also you must remember.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_442'>
He had become a man very early in life.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_443'>
I did not think you would be so early.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_444'>
He did not know what went on in the minds of his superiors.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_445'>
Mops, sir, eagerly answered the sailor at the wheel.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_446'>
Some one had thrust a large sheath-knife into his hand.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_447'>
O'Brien emitted a shriek that sank swiftly to a gurgling sob.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_448'>
Sandel would never become a world champion.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_449'>
Also, she wouldn't walk.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_450'>
To my dearest and always appreciated friend, I submit myself.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_451'>
You used to joyride like the very devil.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_452'>
They saw each other for the first time in Boston.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_453'>
Isaac Ford, the austere soldier of the Lord, the old hypocrite.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_454'>
Eighteen, he added.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_455'>
His reward should have been peace and repose.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_456'>
He was an amphibian and a mountaineer.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_457'>
It was sanctification and salvation.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_458'>
The history of the eighteenth century is written, Ernest prompted.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_459'>
They are not biologists nor sociologists.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_460'>
The more his opponents grew excited, the more Ernest deliberately excited them.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_461'>
By virtue of that power we shall remain in power.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_462'>
One guess will do, Ernest retorted.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_463'>
Take my advice and accept the vacation.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_464'>
I could not agree with Ernest.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_465'>
But such divergence of opinion would constitute no menace to society.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_466'>
It is dog eat dog, and you ate them up.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_467'>
Let us run them for ourselves.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_468'>
It was introduced by Representative Dick of Ohio.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_469'>
Very few people knew of the existence of this law.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_470'>
The very thing, Ernest agreed.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_471'>
Also a fellow Senator, Chauncey Depew, said.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_472'>
Ernest saw in the affair the most sinister import.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_473'>
Then there was the campaign.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_474'>
He was manifestly distressed by my coming.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_475'>
Not a wheel moved in his empire.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_476'>
The reorganization of these countries took the form of revolution.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_477'>
You're going in for grab sharing.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_478'>
The Oligarchy will encourage such ambition and the consequent competition.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_479'>
Violation of this law was made a high misdemeanor and punished accordingly.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_480'>
Without discussion, it was the agents provocateurs who caused the Peasant Revolt.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_481'>
The task we set ourselves was threefold.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_482'>
Many other similar disconcerting omissions will be noticed in the Manuscript.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_483'>
The flower of the artistic and intellectual world were revolutionists.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_484'>
This the Iron Heel foresaw and laid its schemes accordingly.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_485'>
The mob came on, but it could not advance.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_486'>
But why continue the tirade, for tirade it was.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_487'>
After all superfluous flesh is gone what is left is stringy and resistant.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_488'>
Beyond refusing to sell us food, they left us to ourselves.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_489'>
He was a merry monarch, especially so for an Asiatic.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_490'>
What an excited whispering and conferring took place.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_491'>
Jacob Brinker, who was his roadmate, brought the news.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_492'>
Thus he turned the tenets and jargon of psychology back on me.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_493'>
You yellow giant thing of the frost.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_494'>
Never so strange a prophet came up to Jerusalem.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_495'>
We who have endured so much surely can endure a little more.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_496'>
I have seen myself that one man contemplated by Pascal's philosophic eye.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_497'>
One great drawback to farming in California is our long dry summer.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_498'>
I remembered the red wine of the Italian rancho, and shuddered inwardly.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_499'>
I said, and dismissed the matter as not worth thinking about.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_500'>
Then came my boy code.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_501'>
And wherever I ranged, the way lay along alcohol-drenched roads.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_502'>
And as we hurried up town, Joe Goose explained.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_503'>
The scents of strange vegetation blew off the tropic land.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_504'>
The life there was healthful and athletic, but too juvenile.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_505'>
How valiantly I went at it that first day.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_506'>
It would help to tide me along until I got steady employment.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_507'>
Did I possess too much vitality.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_508'>
In his anxiety and solicitude and love they did not count.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_509'>
He had fulfilled his duty and paid properly.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_510'>
He knew what taboos he was violating.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_511'>
Do you value your hide.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_512'>
You should have seen them when they heard me spitting Chinook.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_513'>
He plodded on for half an hour, when the hallucination arose again.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_514'>
Tomorrow or next day it might he gone.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_515'>
But already he had composed himself.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_516'>
Zilla relaxed her sour mouth long enough to sigh her satisfaction.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_517'>
Eggshell is not good to eat.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_518'>
But there was also talk of witchcraft in the village.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_519'>
Yea, I will tell thee.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_520'>
Hans hurled himself upon the prostrate man, striking madly with his fists.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_521'>
And he thought of Oona, and of her words.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_522'>
Nor would it thaw out his hands and feet.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_523'>
The Russian music player, the Count, was her obedient slave.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_524'>
So far as flags were concerned, they were beyond all jurisdiction.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_525'>
New idea, he volunteered, brand new idea.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_526'>
Thirty pounds, said the captain with finality.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_527'>
The very idea of it was preposterous.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_528'>
Captain Doane's orders were swiftly obeyed.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_529'>
Come on, Del Mar challenged.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_530'>
He had a big chimpanzee that was a winner.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_531'>
I am sure it must have been some adventure.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_532'>
That Longfellow chap most likely had written countless books of poetry.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_533'>
His abnormal power of vision made abstractions take on concrete form.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_534'>
I'll tell you, the librarian said with a brightening face.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_535'>
He read his fragments aloud.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_536'>
Typhoid, did I tell you.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_537'>
But she had become an automaton.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_538'>
At the best, they were necessary accessories.
</fileid>
<fileid id='b0001_539'>
You were making them talk shop, Ruth charged him.
</fileid>
</document>
